about 1 back of its first tomorrow attend to stop
honest with the crowd
Pvt Specter
Thanks for having me.
Wait a minute if i can pick 1.
Jumura!
Thank you, too.
How cool. Check out all these posters.
And they're even playing the opening theme song over there.
Hey, Eita, look at the menu. It's pretty cool, too.
The dishes all take their names for the dungeon bosses, see?
Some of these are real blasts from the past.
Yeah, you're right. That's some eagle-eyed vision, Mr. Kamota. Let's see here.
Ooh, they actually look really good. Does everyone know what they want?
Uh-oh. I know Yamada and Rurihime.
But who's this old guy and the one wearing glasses?
That brings back memories.
What about you? Are you into spicy foods, Eita?
If you made me pick, sweets are best.
Looks like they're having a blast.
Rurihime? Who exactly are those two people?
I assume they're part of our guild?
That's Mr. Kamota, and that one's Eita.
Uh, uh, right. Can you tell me a little bit more about them?
Before that, about my character name, I don't play Rurihime.
Huh?
But to tell you the truth, I'm actually wondering who you are.
All right.
We'll be right back to her.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Huh?
Uh... What do you mean?
What is this? Why are you sitting in on our guild's meet-up out of the blue?
Wha...? You are Rurihime, right?
I told you I'm not.
But...
Never mind me. I still want to know who you are.
Hold on just a second. If you're not Rurihime, then where is she? You have to be...
I just told you.
Hey Eita, before we start ordering food, wouldn't it be good for us to introduce ourselves?
Huh?
Oh, that's right, huh? Sorry about that, Akanechi.
So we're on the same page.
I'm Eita Sasaki, age 19. I game online.
I'm also the one who plays as Rurihime.
Nice to meet you.
Akanechi!
Nekama means...
A guy portraying as a woman online where his true appearance and identity remain unknown.
The person representing himself as a woman, or in other cases, it can refer to the act of doing so.
It's an abbreviation of the term Net-Okama, which has been used since even the pre-Internet days of online communications.
Ne... Ka...
No, no, no. You're wrong.
I am a gear that moves my muse, who descended upon the cyberspace sea.
In other words, Rurihime and I are one and the same, while also being totally different.
Low them I to describe this unique state of existence with a cheap term as loaded as Nekama.
Or rather I should say it's not so facile as that.
In the 2D world, Rurihime and I are, if anything, bound by a common destiny.
To put it into words, she's like my goddess, my mother, my bride, and my alter ego.
As soon as a guy starts using a female character, they cry,
Nekama, Nekama, but what do they know, you know?
In that regard, I suppose Rurihime and I have a much more creative relationship.
Not that it's an easy thing for most people to comprehend, but what I'm trying to say is that...
Eita, just a sec.
Not everybody shares your passion.
Hey! I gave you my number and turned to you for advice about being dumped!
Just settle down, Akanechi.
It's all good.
Because that wasn't me, it was Rurihime.
What does that even mean?
Um, uh, hello, I'm Takezo Kamota.
My in-game character name is Takezo as well and is spelled out in English.
I'm usually AFK grinding in the dungeons, so we've never met as our characters before.
And this young lady is Runa.
She's Eita's younger sister, and unbeknownst to most, the model for Rurihime.
How creepy is it to base your character on your own kid's sister?
Uh...
Oh!
And next to you is Akito Yamada.
Though actually, you two already know each other, right?
Huh?
What's he mean, you know each other?
What are you two exactly?
Explain your connection!
Uh...
That's kinda...
I mean...
It's too long a story to explain right now.
It's really complicated.
No, it's not!
We just happened to meet at an event, nothing more!
In a nutshell...
Yeah.
I was hoping I was wrong, but I had a feeling...
I knew it!
She totally hates me!
Oh...
But...
I see...
Hm?
When I saw the two of you in the game, it was you and Eita I was seeing.
But it really did look like you were flirting, so I thought you were a couple!
It was an upperclassman of mine back home, so when he gets totally in character...
I've got to play along.
Yamada!
Wait!
Upperclassman's orders.
Gotcha!
That must be tough.
You said you never had a girlfriend back when we first met.
I thought you might have been lying.
Lying about a thing like that isn't something I do.
Right!
Of course you wouldn't!
I'm glad to hear it!
Wait...
Wha...
What did I just say?
Glad to hear it?
I'm glad to hear it.
Is that what you just said?
Can you elaborate?
Just what did you mean by glad?
Tell me, Akane...
Could it be that you're really in love with Yamada?
No.
I'm so sorry, Akanechi.
My sister is super territorial and she's in the throes of adolescent rebellion, so she can be a bit abrasive.
Really now, Rona? It's so rude to talk to an older girl like that.
No.
Such behavior is uncommon.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
Keep acting like that and you'll have a hard time in life.
You better back off, Nakama!
I'm a romanticist, not an Akama!
Shut up!
Please don't fight!
Excuse me, everybody. Have you all decided what you might want?
I wonder what I should order.
That was startling.
I'll get someone to take out...
Akane, are you okay?
Oh gosh, I'm sorry. It slipped.
Oh, are you hurt? Let's call someone over.
It's fine. I can do it.
You could hurt yourself, so we should let the staff handle it.
I guess you're right.
Excuse me, somebody! We accidentally broke a glass over here!
This is crazy. I mean, I didn't see that coming at all.
What am I gonna do? My face must be so red.
Should I run to the restroom? Would that be weird?
Whatever I do, I've got to pull myself together.
I'll be right back. I have to go make a call.
Okay.
Oh, what are you having? I'll order for you.
Please, order first.
Thank goodness.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Sorry, I think I feel the call of nature.
So he's Ruhihime.
And she's still glaring.
Please enjoy.
Thank you very much.
You feeling better now?
I am. Sorry for the commotion.
I'm just glad you didn't hurt yourself.
Aw, thanks for your concern.
Mr. Komoto's so sweet.
We knew this would be your very first offline meetup with everyone, Akane.
So we were all looking forward to this.
Nobody informed me. This is the worst.
So, how'd you all meet? Have you known each other long?
As fate would have it, us four met in a previous game we were playing.
We migrated over to FOSS when Eita introduced us to it.
Runa here hardly ever logs in these days, though.
We see her maybe once in three months.
I see. Aside from me, everyone at this meetup knows each other.
Eita was so excited about today, saying there was a lovely person joining us that he couldn't wait to welcome into our guild.
Hey, you're not going after my brother too, are you?
Certainly not!
And here I thought you never lied. How's that phone call going, huh?
What's the matter?
For some reason, I got the feeling she wanted me out of her sight immediately.
You stay away from me.
She was giving off that kind of aura.
Ah, so that's how you interpreted things, huh?
I think it's safe to say what Runa said to her had upset her in a major way.
It seemed like Akanechi was just a little embarrassed to me.
Embarrassed about what?
Don't make me say it.
But I won't know what it is unless you say it.
Suppose that's the kind of guy you are.
Not that I mind, though.
Still, having seen Akanechi in real life, she sure is pretty, isn't she?
You told me she was just like her character, so I thought she'd be more childish.
Hmm?
Yamada! Yamada! Yamada!
That's her to a T, though.
Huh?!
But I don't think they look alike at all.
That so?
I mean, the female characters in Phos are all the little girl types, so...
Well, it's not like I can tell the difference between girls.
My friend, you're never gonna find yourself a girlfriend with that kind of attitude.
Isn't giving me a hard time about not having a girlfriend getting old?
I have to say, it used to be a fun past time.
But these days, I'm starting to get worried.
Your indifference towards girls is abnormal, you know?
Hmm.
Did you feel sorry for me?
Did you...?
…
Good-bye.
Thank you very much.
All right, that's it for now.
There's a guild battle tonight, so what do you say we all meet up again online to play later?
Okay!
Deepest apologies for not walking you home, Akanechi.
If only I didn't have a shift today.
What if you get lost again?
Ruri's so worried.
I think I'll be fine.
Hey now, what's the matter, Runa?
Why are you glaring like that?
I don't like her one bit.
Look at her clinging onto Yamada and my brother.
She seems like a bitch.
Oh dear!
Where did you hear a word like that, Runa?
It's always been the four of us playing together.
Why should we bother letting that girl in now?
I swear I'm going to kick her out of our guild if it's the last thing I do.
Hmm...
Hey!
We're headed the same way, so let's go home together!
I impulsively blurted that out, but the conversation's not taking off like I'd hoped.
Hey, Yamada?
Yes?
So tell me, do you all often hang out together like this?
Yes.
Huh.
So you must really get along.
I guess so.
Oh, hey, Eta sure is a fun guy, huh?
He is.
Okay, then...
You're not hurt, are you?
Sorry.
You should switch places with me.
It's okay.
I feel bad.
It's fine.
Thank you very much.
Uh...
Huh?
Oh.
Ah.
It's him.
Whoa.
For a second there, I thought they were staring at me.
I was taken aback by his good looks at first, too.
Could it be that you're really in love with Yamada?
Oh.
When she looked at us, is that what she saw?
Not good, not good.
Yamada's a valued online gamer friend.
Say, uh, Yamada, what are you having for dinner?
Well, I'm not really all that hungry.
Really?
Pudding, maybe.
That's funny.
That will be 128 yen.
Thanks for shopping with us.
Uh, wait.
So you were being serious about that?
Yes.
Do you live alone, Yamada?
And you don't cook at home?
Not at all.
What?
I almost can't believe it.
What do you eat every day?
I buy food from convenience stores and stuff.
Oh, really?
Yamada's a high school student, if I'm remembering right.
Doesn't his mom say anything about that?
No.
I shouldn't pry into someone's family life.
Hmm.
Uh, Yamada!
Do you have some time?
I do?
Fifteen?
No, ten!
Wait here for ten minutes.
I'll be right back.
Hmm.
Yamanah, long time no see!
But I guess people do bounce back.
D destinies.
Yamaru!
Thanks for waiting for me.
Are you doing okay there?
I haven't.
Or I'm like, my life depended on it since high school.
What's with these big bags?
What did you pack?
Oh, this here's curry.
I'm pretty sure you don't cook rice at home.
So I brought some frozen rice too.
I just made this curry earlier today.
So it should last for at least two days.
Since I'm strapped for cash this month, there's not much meat in it.
But to make up for that, I'll give you the salad and pickled veggies I just bought at the convenience store.
No, that's not...
I wouldn't feel right taking this.
And you just said your money's tight, so...
Trust me, you have to eat right or you won't grow properly.
Sure, but I...
Pudding is for dessert.
Well, yeah, but still...
Here, from one guildmate to another.
But...
That's your phone ringing.
Oh, it's mine?
Wonder who it is.
Momo maybe?
Huh, I don't know this number.
Yes?
Hello?
Uh...
This is...
Runa.
Oh, hey, what's up?
I got your number from my brother.
Sorry I didn't ask you first.
Oh, that's okay.
I'm sorry for being so rude to you.
I know you came all the way there to meet us.
My brother told me to apologize, too.
What?
Don't worry, I don't mind one bit.
Who doesn't get nervous when meeting people for the first time?
Then, if you want, I'd like to hang out again.
The next time, I want to do it right.
And get along with you.
Runa?
Okay.
Sure.
You said next Saturday, right?
Yeah, sounds good.
Great.
I'm looking forward to it, too.
Bye.
I'm gonna hang out with Runa next weekend.
Uh, right.
I could hear.
I thought she couldn't stand the sight of me.
I'm thrilled.
Now I'm getting super curious about what Runa's like in-game.
Do you know Yamada?
A little.
What's her job class, and what does she use?
Ooh, is she a mage?
I would love to see her sometime.
What level is she, I wonder?
That's great.
Yeah, I'm gonna add Runa's number to my contacts.
She said Saturday, right?
Runa Sasaki.
Tutoring job.
As I thought.
Hmm.
Did I hear her wrong?
Today I'm going to show you all the avatars Tsurihima likes to use.
First up, Alice's Flower Clock Set.
It's a really popular avatar that I tend to wear every now and again.
Next we have the Priest's Holy Robe Max.
When I remove this avatar, my armor's on full display.
Now behold, the Red Roses for the Queen Set.
It's gorgeous, though I don't really wear it that often.
Last but not least, my usual.
It has the best stats and it's my favorite.
My heartfelt gratitude to you all for watching.
If you enjoyed this display, look forward to more hot tips from Yurihima, so stay tuned.
Okay, me.